in big moments and they enjoy the atmosphere,
在关键时刻,他们享受着这种氛围,
they enjoy everything that goes into those situations.
他们享受着那些情况下的一切。
I mean, Martinez, once again in your career, you stand up.
马丁内斯，你的职业生涯中你再一次站出来
and you are able to progress your team to another stage.
你又带领你的团队再往前进一步。
Just tell me how you are feeling right now, man.
你现在感觉如何,伙计。
Well, it's been a hell of a ride all my career.
嗯,这是一段非常艰难的旅程,我整个职业生涯都是这样。
I always think I'm a believer and a hard worker, and it was my destiny to win here again.
我一直认为我是一个信徒和努力的人，命中注定要在这里取胜
I mean, I learned something new today in terms of just a rule for myself.
今天我学到了一条新规则。
I didn't know in terms of that a goalkeeper could be booked.
我不知道门将会因为超出规定区域被出示黄牌。
outside of the regulation zone and then it doesn't regulate in terms of two yellow cards and two red cards.
而且不会按照两黄变一红的规则执行。（点球大战前的黄牌不带入点球大战）
I've got a bad reputation for time waiting because the other goalie was doing exactly the same thing and I get booked after the third minute.
我因为一直拖延时间而名声不佳,因为对方门将也在做同样的事情,但我在第三分钟后就被出示了黄牌。
and we're losing the game so i don't know what the rave went for one for me
而且我们当时正在落后于对手,所以我不知道他为什么只警告我
and then again there was no ball in the penalty spot and I'm asking for a ball to a ball boy
然后又是在点球点上没有足球,我向球童要了一个足球
and then I get booked I just don't and understand the rules.
结果我又被出示了一张黄牌。我真的不太理解这些规则。
Let's talk about the positives, because how do you keep so composed and so controlled in those moments?
让我们谈谈积极的一面,因为你是如何在那些时刻保持如此冷静和控制的?
I mean, we've seen your history in terms of your penalties, but with the tension that was on you, the crowd that was on your back, how did you remain so controlled in that situation?
我们都看到了你曾经在点球大战中的表现,但在那种压力和观众的嘘声下,你是如何保持冷静的?
I always say that I own my career, I own my personal performances.
我总是说,我掌控着自己的职业生涯,掌控着自己的表现。
I know my team needs me in those moments, they always do.
我知道我的团队在那些时刻总是需要我
Even yesterday we were watching Real Madrid vs Man City.
就像昨天我们观看皇马对曼城的比赛一样。
And the man has been saying, like, if we go to penalty, maybe we go to penalty.
大家都在说,如果进入点球大战的话,我们就踢点球吧。
So in my head, I'm always, you know, in those moments, I own my box.
所以在我的脑海里,我总是在那些时刻掌控住自己的禁区。
I think finally, just for you, it feels like something special is brewing in here.
对你来说，这里似乎有一些特别的事情正在酝酿
It feels like...
感觉就像...
A lot of the players when they came in here, they said the road to Athens, that's what they're screaming.
很多球员进来时，他们都在喊着要进军雅典
Do you feel it as well in terms of, I know there's another big journey in the semi-final,
你也有同感吗?我知道半决赛还有一段很长的路要走
But do you feel like there is something special right now?
但你觉得现在有种特殊的感觉吗?
Yeah, look, this group of players and the managers,
是的,看,这支球队的球员和教练组
It's special.
都很特别。
Their owners are really involved as well.
俱乐部老板也非常支持我们。
Wes and Nasef, they're always behind us.
Wes和Nasef，他们总是支持我们。
因此，感觉我们即将去做一些特别的事情。
it feels like we're going to do something special.
I don't know if it's Champions League,
无论是欧冠还是欧协联
I don't know if it's a conference league, but we will try to do everything we can for this football club.
但我们会为这家俱乐部尽自己最大的努力。
I'm using these words very carefully.
我在小心翼翼地措辞。
Make sure you get out of France.
确保你平安离开法国。
Very safe and sound, my friend.
一路平安,我的朋友。
Enjoy it.
好好享受吧。